

# Sergey Moshkin QA Engineer

location: Warsaw, Poland

email: sergey.moshkin92@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/aezakmi

Hello, I've been working as a QA Engineer for 3.5+ years commercial experience and I'm looking for new opportunities and possibility to unlock my potential.

I have expertise in Web (UI/API) and Mobile testing(Android & iOS), also I'm doing my best to learn Automation testing.

# **Skills**

- Full testing life cycle, including test documentation creation (test reports, test cases, check-lists, reports)
- Functional/non-functional testing of Web/Mobile applications
- Cross-Browser and Cross-Platform testing
- English A2 level

### **Tools**

TestRail, Zephyr, Postman, Browser DevTools, DataGrip, Jmeter, Charles, Kibana, Xcode, Android Studio, FireBase, Jira, Basic Commands Linux, MacOS, Windows, Linux, iOS, Android, Fork

# **Educational Background**

Educational center "My Monday" 2019 Manual Testing Course

# **Hobbies**

- Cycling
- Board games
- Traveling to cool new places
- Watching cult films

# **Work Experience**

#### **QA** Engineer

KoronaPay Europe - full-time - (Fintech project, Mobile); Nov 2021 - present

- Mobile testing(android & iOS);
- Work with Test Documentation(creation of bug-reports, test cases and etc.);
- Full circle of testing;
- Working with SDLS, Agile methodologies;
- Creating automation cases for iOS and Learning js+Webdriver.io framework for AT;
- Working with xCode and Android studio;
- Working with Charles(mocking api requests and etc.);

## **QA** Engineer

SmartUpGlobal - full-time - (Cashback project and etc.) Sep 2020 to Nov 2021

- Building the Software Testing processes, improving and optimization QA processes;
- Web & Mobile testing(work with Android Studio, xCode emulator, simulator);
- Mentoring of Junior QA;
- Work with Test Documentation(creation of bug-reports, test cases and etc);
- SDLS, Agile methodologies;
- GUI and Functional testing;
- Usability testing;
- Security testing basics;

## **QA** Engineer

CrediVault - part-time - (Blockchain project, Web);

*Jul 2020 - Sep 2020* 

- Manual Testing
- Work with Test Documentation;
- SDLS, Agile methodologies;
- Usability testing;

## Junior QA Engineer

System Technologies - full-time - (Fintech project, Web, Mobile); Oct 2019 - Sep 2020

- Manual Testing
- SDLS, Agile methodologies;
- GUI and Functional testing;
- Work with Test Documentation(creating check-lists and test cases);
- Learning client-server applications architecture (HTTP/HTTPS, REST, SOAP, API, CSS, JS, XML, JSON, cookie);